tendernews.com 2012-12-04

# Invitation to tender india on the web construction tenders printing tenders bids public tenders news india

Policy Statements

Tender news INDIA is committed to protecting your privacy and security. From time to time we may invite you to supply personal information in order for us to provide you with services (such as access as subscriber, trial member, email newsletters etc. 

Tender news INDIA is committed to protecting your privacy and security. From time to time we may invite you to supply personal information in order for us to provide you with services (such as access as subscriber, trial member, email newsletters etc.

In order to deliver such services, we will need to process and store your personal information and may need to transfer it to the relevant partner(s), to affiliates of Tender news India for processing both locally and globally. By submitting your personal information, you consent to such processing and transfer in connection with such orders, offers or services and for any other purposes. We will never willfully disclose personal information about you to any third party other than to process an order or unless we are under a legal obligation to do so. 

**Links**  
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that tendernews.com india is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

**Monitoring, Logs & Cookies **   
We at Tender News India use IP addresses, cookies etc. to analyze trends, administer the site, track site use, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. If you have any comments or concerns regarding our Privacy Policy or want copy of information we hold about you, feel free to contact us.
